planet-f1.com 2008-12-19

# Front Page - Planet-F1 News - The Very Latest Formula One News, Galleries And Test Reports from planet-f1.com

## Planet F1 Privacy Policy

We at 365 Media Group Ltd, (incorporating this site and all of the sites within our network - as seen on the footer of this website), strongly believe in protecting the confidentiality and security of information we collect about individuals. The material below describes our privacy policy and describes how we treat the information we receive about you if you interact with any of our sites.  

**Why We Need to Know About You**  

We need to know about you so that we can provide you with information on products and services and better target our sports content offering to your interests. What we need to know about you includes your address, age and preferences. 

**How We Learn About You**  

What we know about you we get mostly from you. But we may also have to find out more about you from other sources in order to make sure that what we know about you is correct and complete. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from competitions, message boards, suggestions and transactional areas. 

**Your Right To Opt Out**  

At our points of data collection, you have the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to "opt in" or "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from group companies and/or third parties on whose behalf we may send out information. Further, notwithstanding any opt out of promotional information by the user, we reserve the right to contact you regarding account status, changes to our service agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. You can request to "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time and all promotional emails we send you allow you this facility. Also, upon request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts functionally to delete you and your personal information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete a your entry without some residual information due to backups and records of deletions. 

**How We Protect What We Know About You**  

We treat what we know about you confidentially. Our employees take care in handling your information. They may get information about you only when there is a good reason to do so. We take steps to make our databases secure and to safeguard the information we have about you. 

**How We Use and Disclose What We Know About You**  

We may use anything we know about you to help us serve you better. We will not disclose your information to any third party save for the following exceptions: 

\- To help us process questions you may have about a purchase, registration or other inquiry you may have.  

\- To confirm or correct what we know about you.  

\- To help us or law enforcement agencies prevent fraud, money laundering, terrorism and other crimes.  

\- To allow for verification of what we know about you.  

\- Data processing requirements.  

\- Assisting an agency perform research for us.  

\- Compliance with the law or request of a government agency for example, complying with a search warrant.  

\- Compliance with an audit our business.  

\- If we sell all or any part of our business or merge with another company. 

Generally, we will disclose only the information we consider reasonably necessary to disclose. 

**How You Can See and Correct Your Information**  

Generally, we will let you review what we know about you if you ask us in writing or email. If you tell us that what we know about you is incorrect, we will review it. If we agree with you, we will correct our records. 

**Third Party Data Collection**  

You should be aware that sites within the group might sometimes permit third parties to offer you subscription, registration-based services, promotions or competitions through our network. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information to other parties. 

**Sharing Your Data in Public Areas of our Sites**  

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) on any of our message boards, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control. 

**How We Use IP Addresses**  

We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problems with our server or to administer our websites. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information that helps us understand user requirements. This specific information will only be used within our organisation and we will only share or use this information on an aggregate basis. 

**How We Use Cookies**  

We collect non-personal information and data through the standard operation of our servers or through the use of cookies. 

Cookies are small text files a web site used to recognise repeat users, facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the site, track usage, follow site behaviour and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a your system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. 

Cookies can help you for example by delivering content specific to your interests, or to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our sites employ the services of an outside companies to serve and appropriately target online advertisements and track site usage. To do this, their software collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. 

Users should be aware that we cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for us. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g. customised delivery of information) available on our web sites. 

**Links to Other Sites**  

Our site contains links to other sites outside of our control. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

Thank you for reading our privacy policy and thank you for choosing our network of sites as your reliable source of news and views on the Internet. If you have any questions about anything contained in this policy, you can contact our Customer Relations Team at: 365 Media Group, 3rd Floor, Apsley House, 78 Wellington Street, Leeds, LS1 2EQ, United Kingdom or e-mail us at [customerrelations@365mediagroup.co.uk](mailto:customerrelations@365mediagroup.co.uk). 

The foregoing policies are effective as of 1 May 2008. 365 Media Group Ltd reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
